{
  "quizfragen": [
    {
      "Frage": "Was ist 2+2",
      "a": 1900,
      "b": 4,
      "c": 40,
      "Antwort": "b"
    },
    {
      "Frage": "Was ist 39+75",
      "a": 114,
      "b": 209,
      "c": 96,
      "Antwort": "a"
    },
    {
      "Frage": "Was ist 555 + 196",
      "a": 753,
      "b": 689,
      "c": 751,
      "Antwort": "c"
    },
    {
      "Frage": "Was ist 121 / 11",
      "a": 14,
      "b": 12,
      "c": 11,
      "Antwort": "c"
    },
    {
      "Frage": "Was ist 56 / 8",
      "a": 4,
      "b": 7,
      "c": 6,
      "Antwort": "b"
    },
    {
      "Frage": "Was ist 2*7",
      "a": 14,
      "b": 12,
      "c": 21,
      "Antwort": "a"
    },
    {
      "Frage": "Was ist 16 * 5",
      "a": 1900,
      "b": 4,
      "c": 40,
      "Antwort": "b"
    },
    {
      "Frage": "Was ist 70 - 40",
      "a": 35,
      "b": 40,
      "c": 30,
      "Antwort": "b"
    },{
      "Frage": "Was ist 587-638",
      "a":-57,
      "b": 4,
      "c": -51,
      "Antwort": "c"
    },{
      "Frage": "Was ist 26*3-39",
      "a": 49,
      "b": 78,
      "c": 39,
      "Antwort": "b"
    }
  ]
}





